
Welcome to Gradle 9.3.0!

Here are the highlights of this release:
 - Test reporting improvements
 - Error and warning improvements
 - Build authoring improvements

For more details see https://docs.gradle.org/9.3.0/release-notes.html

Starting a Gradle Daemon, 1 incompatible Daemon could not be reused, use --status for details

[Incubating] Problems report is available at: file:///C:/Users/Admin/Downloads/AdbConsole/AdbConsole/build/reports/problems/problems-report.html

Deprecated Gradle features were used in this build, making it incompatible with Gradle 10.

You can use '--warning-mode all' to show the individual deprecation warnings and determine if they come from your own scripts or plugins.

For more on this, please refer to https://docs.gradle.org/9.3.0/userguide/command_line_interface.html#sec:command_line_warnings in the Gradle documentation.
